Welcome to The Pines at Bristol Center for Health and Rehabilitation.
I am Kelly Doobie and it would be my pleasure to give you a tour of our warm and
inviting center.
A under the guidance of National Healthcare Associates,
we take great pride in our mission to provide kindness, compassion,
service, and excellence to our guests in their journey to better health.
Our professional staff is available to answer any questions or concerns
24 7.
This is one of our private rooms that we offer here at The Pines.
Each room has its own closet, nightstand, dresser,
and cable TV to make our guests feel at home.
Our commitment to innovation allows us to advance our best in class
programs beyond what you would typically see in a skilled nursing environment.
Our industry leading passport rehabilitation program is the right choice
to help you transition back home.
We provide a comprehensive array of specialized services and programs
that include physical, occupational,
and speech therapies up to seven days a week designed to get you back
home safely.
Our team will help you feel supported on your journey to wellness so you
can focus on your recovery. Dining,
nutrition and recreation are vital components in the journey to better health.
In
Addition to breakfast, lunch, and dinner,
we are proud to offer in any time menu for our guests to enjoy throughout their
stay.
As part of our approach to ensuring your continued health,
we are proud to offer our passport to home nurse practitioner who
will help coordinate your care so you can remain home safely.
Whether
You join us for a brief stay or we'll be calling The Pines at Bristol Center for
Health and Rehabilitation your home, we would be honored to care for you.